[Veil of Shadows]
[Episode 1]
Why's someone lying there?
What's going on?
[Seventh day of the tenth month]
Someone's dead!
[The Well-Woven House]
Did you hear?
Last night,
they found another body.
So scary!
[Fourteenth day of the tenth month]
Again, his heart
was ripped out.
I heard a high-rank demon's here.
So we can't stay
in Luo'an anymore.
Now the whole town's in panic.
That demon will surely
keep killing and taking hearts.
Who knows who'll be next?
[Twenty-first day of the tenth month]
How terrifying!
To keep their wedding going,
the Wei family specially hired
a demon hunter from the Shilin Sect.
- This isn't just any demon hunter, - Good.
- That's it! - but someone with a flower on his forehead!
Good.
Miss, you are...?
I'm the Wei family's bride-to-be's...
cousin.
My name's Yu Wei.
Please, follow me.
[Wei Qing, head of the Wei family]
Here, Shengwei.
[Yu Shengwei, daughter of the Yu family]
Master Wei.
[Luo Wei, steward of the Wei mansion]
The wedding dress will be done in two days.
I'll deliver it to the Yu mansion myself.
Guess we should go pray at the Dragon Deity Temple.
May we stay deeply in love,
and grow old together.
What do you think?
Come on, Wei Qing.
The Dragon Deity doesn't handle that stuff.
[Liu Weixue, Wei Qing's cousin]
Master Wei.
Miss Yu's cousin has arrived.
You are...?
Shengwei.
I know it's been a while,
but you really don't recognize me?
I'm your cousin,
Yu Wei.
Oh, I remember now.
You're Yu Wei.
[Twenty-fourth day of the tenth month]
I've got a hostage now!
Dare you chase me anymore?
Ow, that hurts!
What's your problem?
What kind of weirdo are you?
Why'd you hang me up?
Untie me, now!
You demon hunters are something else.
Go after that greater fox demon
that's been killing and stealing hearts.
Why come after me,
an innocent little weasel?
Save it.
Get in!
No, please!
Thank you, kind sir,
for saving my life a second time.
No problem, Miss Yu.
Second time?
Master Wei's arranged
a dinner banquet
to thank you, Master.
Please rest here for now.
Thanks.
[Wu Shiguang]
So?
[You Chi, low-rank weasel demon]
Did I nail my act?
All thanks
to my majestic black smoke.
Absolutely brilliant!
Half a month ago,
a broken-tail fox attacked Miss Yu.
It must be linked to the heart-stealing one.
Otherwise,
those arrogant demon hunters from the Shilin Sect
wouldn't have been guards
for an ordinary family.
You Chi!
Come in!
Yu told me
how you were kind enough
to save her half a month ago.
She could've died.
Thank you, Master.
It was nothing.
But that time,
it was really dangerous.
[Half a month ago]
Help!
[Seventh day of the tenth month]
Eight tails...
A broken-tail fox!
Run!
That fox demon moves without a trace.
Really terrifying.
Shengwei,
have your favorite chestnut cake.
It may comfort you.
Master Wu, you're truly amazing.
If you hadn't chased that fox demon off,
my cousin's heart
would've been ripped out too.
I didn't exactly chase it off.
And that day marked
the first murder
in this whole heart-stealing case.
That broken-tail fox
must be the culprit.
It might've been hiding in this mansion,
so it will try again
to harm Miss Yu.
Master Wu,
are you serious?
The air above this estate is thick with demonic energy.
I fear a high-rank demon has taken root here.
Master Wei,
if you're willing to hire me as a house guard,
I can definitely protect Miss Yu.
That's great!
Although Master Wu is just a wandering hunter
with no real background,
although
he couldn't actually defeat
the fox demon last time,
although
he probably still doesn't know
where the fox demon is
or how to guard against it,
although no one knows
if he could win if it does show up...
one thing's sure...
he's so handsome,
with such a great build.
Having him stay
by my cousin's side,
Shengwei will surely be "safe."
Yeah, sure thing!
Master Wu,
see you later!
I thought it was a sure thing,
but Wei Qing's got such a small mind!
So petty.
The one
who really wants us gone
isn't Wei Qing,
but this cousin of hers.
Who's there?
Rucui.
Is it time yet?
Rucui?
Quiet.
Follow my lead.
Hey,
are we sure
this isn't dangerous?
The heart thefts started on Oct 7th.
Every seven days, someone dies.
Today,
the fox demon should strike again.
Nothing ventured, nothing gained.
If you want to catch the heart-stealing demon
and claim the bounty from the Shilin Sect,
then shut up, okay?
So the fox demon wanted to kill Miss Yu that day,
but failed,
so it killed someone else instead.
Then every seven days after,
it kills one person on schedule.
Yeah, that's it!
I'm just too smart.
Are you even listening to me?
Yeah.
[Twenty-eighth day of the tenth month, auspicious for weddings]
Congratulations!
[The Well-Woven House]
Congrats!
Please, come in!
Come on in!
Just put it over there.
Right this way!
Come, this way please!
What a perfect day!
Congrats!
Come on, right inside!
[Ji Ling]
The nine-tailed fox's magic is right in my hand.
[Li Jie]
Impressive.
Let's go!
Alright!
[The Well-Woven House]
Please, come in!
- Come on in! - This way, please!
- No need for formalities. - Congratulations!
Congratulations!
- Congrats! - Right this way!
Gentlemen,
it's crowded and busy inside.
Please leave your names
and your wedding gifts,
so I can record them properly.
Well, the gifts...
The gifts...
Li Jie.
What are you looking at me for?
Congratulations.
All these human customs
are such a hassle.
This door's flimsy.
I could smash it with one swing.
Rude.
[The Well-Woven House]
Oh, Master Qi!
Your presence honors our humble home!
Madame Zhao,
you've arrived!
Come in, please!
You're not Miss Yu.
Miss Yu
doesn't have a vixen face like that.
And you're not Master Wei.
Master Wei
wouldn't hold a knife to me.
You're so eager?
They say
the first night together is priceless.
How could I not be eager?
Since we're now wed,
then...
we should be open with each other!
I never thought
my husband would have two faces.
Too bad
one woman shouldn't serve two husbands.
That makes sense.
So, how about
you let me down first?
Well then, sir,
you'll have to
take that dagger away from me first.
Trying to leave?
Such a beautiful vase,
and you have no taste for elegance.
Someone as beautiful as me,
and you have no taste either.
Tonight, I'm divorcing you!
So?
Pretty clever.
Isn't that Steward Luo of this family?
Why is she sneaking around
in her own house?
Something's off.
Let's check it out!
Who are you?
Her accomplices?
What's going on?
Why are you stopping me?
You reek of demonic energy.
You're a fox demon!
She's that heart-eating demon.
Heaven really is fair.
It gives you such a handsome face,
but no brains to go with it.
Groom,
why the sudden change of your face?
Your opponent
is me.
You have no sacred power?
Does that
stop me from fighting you?
Who exactly are you guys?
I'll ask you
the same question.
I'm the demon hunter Wu Shiguang.
Since when do demon hunters
have to worry about so much,
even playing the groom?
I'm pretending to be the groom
for one reason only...
to catch a demon.
What a coincidence.
We're demon hunters too.
We're also here to catch demons.
But unlike you back-alley,
rogue demon hunters,
we're official demon hunters from the Shilin Sect,
sent here
to investigate the heart-stealing case.
This is the Shilin Sect's
demon hunter commander,
Li Jie.
Stunned now?
An ice-wielding demon.
Sure enough,
you're the one we're after!
What grudge do we have?
I don't even know you.
Trying to run?
It's you!
Sir,
save me...
Let... let her go!
Sir,
what's going on?
Who's there?
Still trying to flee?
Thank you, sir, for saving me.
Well...
You're thanking the wrong person.
The groom saved you.
Thank him instead!
Thank you, kind sir.
You're welcome!
What are those red threads
made of?
I guess
it's blood.
Submit now,
or die trying?
It's your choice.
Do I look like I'm struggling?
I'm a demon hunter too,
here to catch demons.
What crime have I committed?
Fine.
Now the whole room's full of demon hunters,
isn't it?
Don't count me in.
I'm no demon hunter.
I'm a respectable woman.
Don't bother denying it!
We traced the demonic energy
right here.
You're the nine-tailed fox stealing hearts!
How terrifying!
Just now,
was she trying to rip out my heart?
Me?
A heart-eating demon?
Are you joking,
or serious?
- I... - Who has time
to joke with a fox demon like you?
You're the sect's demon hunter commander.
And you?
What's your identity?
Me?
Sir!
What should I call you?
My name is Ji Ling.
Ji means "life's a journey,"
and Ling means "hearts that beat as one."
Stay here,
and don't run off, okay?
Sir!
Please don't leave me alone!
This female demon is really terrifying!
I'm so scared!
So scary!
So scary...
You demon!
[Li Mao, wedding guest of the Wei family]
[Tao Xi, Li Mao's wife]
Weimiao Pavilion...
Blood...
It's frost.
It's not even winter yet.
Why is there all this frost?
It's demon magic.
Those prayer beads are amazing.
What's their story?
Don't touch them.
Keep them there.
You're so thoughtful.
Whatever you say.
And you're so clever.
Thanks to you tipping me off,
I was able to prepare.
Wangyan,
the groom's a fake.
He's here to catch fox demons.
Be careful.
Don't let him
make it real,
or turn the tables on you.
I thought we'd guarded against one,
and now two more show up.
That Ji Ling guy
and his long-blade friend
won't be easy either.
But the one really hard to shake
is that guy who won't let me go,
Wu Shiguang.
Oh yeah?
I don't believe it.
Wangyan,
want to make a bet?
Broken-tail fox,
it really is you.
Miss Yu?
I asked you to gather some intel.
Did you get it all?
Of course!
There are 952 weasels in Luo'an City.
From street gossip
to corner rumors,
they know everything.
Let's start with the bride,
Miss Yu.
She's Luo'an's
famous embroiderer,
especially skilled
at stitching birds and beasts.
Now, Luo Wei.
This woman's something else.
A month ago,
the Wei family's business faced a crisis,
almost went bankrupt.
Then Luo Wei appeared out of nowhere
and turned things around.
After that, she joined the Wei mansion
and became the steward.
Everyone in the house
fears and respects her.
And gossip says
she's got a thing for Wei Qing.
So,
she really dislikes Miss Yu.
As for Liu Weixue,
he's Wei Qing's distant cousin.
The Liu family's been generals for generations.
But despite all his skill,
Liu Weixue refuses
to go to war.
- Half a month ago, - Go...
he fled an arranged marriage and came here.
- Bring the wine! - Word on the street is
he might be interested in Luo Wei.
Quick, bring the medicine wine!
What's all this?
So lively late at night?
And Yu Wei
grew up in the countryside,
not from around here.
Their families
rarely interact.
So her showing up for the feast
is pretty strange.
Oh, quite a crowd here.
Miss Yu Wei!
Weren't you supposed to stay in your room?
Why'd you come out?
It's so dangerous!
Since you called her a demon,
how could I stay
in the same room with her?
Plus,
she totally wrecked my clothes.
So I came here
to change into new ones.
So, sir,
do I look good?
Yeah... good.
What's wrong?
Where's the bride I tied up?
Darling,
are you looking for me?
I followed the broken-tail fox here.
But the moment I entered this room,
it vanished.
What do you mean?
I mean,
among all of you here,
one of you
is the heart-stealing killer I'm after,
the broken-tail fox.
[The runaway fox's hiding in the Wei mansion]
Wu Wangyan,
proceed to Luo'an at once
and bring Xiaowei back.
Understood.
What about me?
My mission
is still to assist her?
Your mission
is to get close
to a young man named Ji Ling.
He is your fated one.
Fated one?
Wangyan,
what does this mean?
You hear that?
All five of you
are suspects!
And you two
are no simple cases either.
Bai Ze has brought news
of the nine-tailed fox, Xiaowei.
[Shilin Sect, Scale Cave]
Right now, she's hiding in the Wei mansion
in Luo'an.
Li Jie,
it's time to bring her back.
Understood.
♪It's your light♪
♪Your storms, your watchful eyes♪
♪That set the night alight♪
♪And lead me through the fight♪
♪Jade in the lake, sand in my hand♪
♪Let bitter seeds grow, let fate bloom♪
♪Face in the mirror, veiled in mist♪
♪Till snow has kissed dark hair to white♪
♪Night lamp burning by the old table♪
♪Stitch by stitch, mending moonlight♪
♪The dancing light, the shattered wave♪
♪Are all my helpless, drifting haze♪
♪The boiling frost, the stubborn stare♪
♪Are all the pride I'll never wear♪
♪Your shoulder, your tear-bright eyes♪
♪Are the strength that lifts my dreams to the skies♪
♪Stay with me, let's gaze above♪
♪Nowhere to rest, nowhere to hide♪
♪Bare in body yet boundless inside♪
♪Nothing to seek, nothing to erase♪
♪Like water gone, like the formless moon♪
♪Let every dream and wild desire♪
♪Forge the edge that lifts us higher♪
♪Bells through endless time, sun and moon alike in shine♪
♪Love and hate all earn their crown♪
♪It's your light♪
♪Your storms, your watchful eyes♪
♪That set the night alight♪
♪And lead me sailing afar♪